[Ousiniba's Vlog: Reading your comments]
Volg d'Ousiniba: Lecture de vos commentaires
Hello everyone, your friendly neighbourhood lotus here.
Bonjour, Lotus est là.
Believe it or not, I actually do read your comments under every episode.
Croyez-le ou non, je lis vos commentaires sous tous les épisodes.
Here's one from "Yamada's Fan" on Weibo:
Envoici un de "Fan de Yamaa" sur weibo:
"I hope the teacher gives Ouba more English homework,
"J'espère que lae professeur donne Ouba plus de devoirs d'anglais,
so that we will have more vlogs to watch."
pour qu'on ait plus de vlogs à regarder."
Hmph. Then you will lose me.
Hmph. Alors vous allez me perdre.
"Dumbass Jiuqi" on Bilibili said:
"Stupide Jiuqi" sur Bilibili a dit:
"I want to know when is my husband Muzha coming back?"
"Je veux savoir quand est-ce que mon mari Muzha revient?"
"I am not, I have not! I belong to myself."
"Je ne suis pas, je n'ai pas! Je m'appartiens à moi-même."
"Is anyone interested in looking at me?"
"Quelqu'un veut me regarder?"
A comment from "Lonely Whisperer of the Night" on Bilibili:
Un commentaire de "Murmureur Solitaire de la Nuit" sur Bilibili:
"Jinzha gives off wifey vibes."
"Jinzha a des vibes de femme mariée"
Are you sure?
Es-tu sûr'e?
"How?"
"Comment?"
"I never disappoint."
"Je ne déçois jamais."
Here is one from "The Fish You Are Not ddd" on Weibo:
En voici un de "Le Poisson Que Tu N'es Pas ddd" sur weibo:
"It is said by some that asking students to attend zoom classes,
"Il est dit par certain'e's que demander des élèves à participer aux classes en ligne
is much like asking Sun the Monkey to guard the peach orchard."
est comme demander à Sun le Singe de guarder le verger des pêches"
"Some" is a wise one.
"Certain'e's" est un'e sage
I will have to invite Sun the Monkey to come along to my classes next time.
Je vais devoir inviter Sun le Singe de venir participer à mes classes la prochaine fois
"Ink-wash Ruihua" on Bilibili said:
"Ruihua à l'Encre" sur Bilibili a dit:
"Are you on? Please gacha a Houge* for me."
"tu es en ligne ? Tu peux me gacha Houge* pour moi stp."
You should keep dreaming, there is nothing you can't find in one.
Tu devrais continuer de rêver, il n'y a rien que tu puisses trouver dans un.
A comment from
Un commentaire de
"The Lantern Lights of New Year Call for Your Return" on Weibo:
"Les Lumières des Lanternes du Nouvel An Appelle pour Ton Retour" sur Weibo:
"108 ways to cook lotus roots."
"108 façons de cuire des racines de lotus."
Hmph. I will be gone before the end of it.
Umph. Je serais parti bien avant la fin.
"Moqi TAT Moqi"
"Moqi TAT Moqi"
on Weibo said:
sur Weibo a dit:
"Why is Muzha referred to as Erge,
"Pourquoi Muzha est surnommé Erge,
but Jinzha is called by his name?
mais Jinzha est appelé par son nom?
Is Dage that disrespected in the household?"
Dage est si peu respecté dans la maison?"
"Calling someone by their name is but another way to express love!"
"Appeler quelqu'un par son nom est une autre façon d'exprimer son amour!"
A comment on Weibo by
Un commentaire sur Weibo par
"When The Snow Has Fallen, The Blossom Is Heard. Meryl":
"Quand la Neige est Tombée, l'Eclosion Est Entendue. Meryl":
"I like the sound of an elite level English course hahahaha!"
"J'aime l'idée d'un cours d'anglais de niveau d'élite hahahaha!"
I will gift it to you right now.
Je vais vous l'offrir tout de suite.
"Shishishi" on Bilibili said:
"Shishishi" sur Bilibili a dit:
"The pyjamas from Jinzha are so cute!
"Les pyjamas de Jinzha sont super adorables!
I love both of Ouba's pyjamas sets, I want them badly!
J'aime les deux set de pyjamas d'Ouba, je les veux trop!
But of course what I want most is Ouba himself!"
Mais bien sûr ce je veux le plus est Ouba lui-même!"
"Our little brother is ours!"
"Notre petit frère est à nous!"
And that is the end of our comment reading episode,
Et c'est la fin de notre épisode de lecture de commentaires,
See you next time.
à la prochaine.
If this video gets more than 30,000 likes, I will put on some women's clothes for you all.
Si cette vidéo a plus de 30 000 like, je mettrais des habits de femme pour vous.
Goodbye.
Au revoir.